Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG.37.4
New York University Archives
- Series I: Director's Files, 67843
  - Subseries B: Individuals, 68056
    - Jean Starobinski, 1979-1980; cuid4541; 68077 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Roger Straus, undated; cuid4542; 68076 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Pep Subiros, undated; cuid4543; 68075 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - William Taylor, 1979-1988; cuid4544; 68074 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273253
    - Gerald M. Turkel, undated; cuid4545; 68073 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - A. Richard Turner, 1982-1986; cuid4546; 68072 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - A. Richard Turner Correspondence, 1991-1993; cuid4547; 68071 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Brian Urquhart, 1982-1988; cuid4548; 68070 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Luisa Valenzuela, 1979-1981; cuid4549; 68069 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Kirk Varnedoe, 1988; cuid4550; 68068 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Xavier Rubert De Ventos, 1977; cuid4551; 68067 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Ileana Verzea, undated; cuid4552; 68066 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Nicholas Wahl, 1979-1986; cuid4553; 68065 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Eric Wanner, 1986; cuid4554; 68064 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Aileen Ward, 1979-1988; cuid4555; 68063 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Ann Warnford-Davis, 1984; cuid4556; 68062 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Annette Weiner, 1987-1988; cuid4557; 68061 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Monique Wittig - Dossier, 1980-1982; cuid4558; 68060 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - K.D. Wolff, undated; cuid4559; 68059 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Gwendolyn Wright, 1985; cuid4560; 68058 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Carol Yaple, 1982; cuid4561; 68057 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Subseries C: Institutions, 67943
    - AAAS - Denver, 1976-1977; cuid4562; 68055 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - AAAS - Publications, 1977; cuid4563; 68054 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - All Souls, Oxford, 1985; cuid4564; 68053 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - American Academy in Rome, undated; cuid4565; 68052 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - American Sociological Association, 1977-1981; cuid4566; 68051 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Architectural Association (London), 1979-1980; cuid4567; 68050 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - ASA Meetings, 1979; cuid4568; 68049 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Aspen Institute, 1977-1983; cuid4569; 68048 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Atlantic Monthly, 1981-1984; cuid4570; 68047 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273261
    - Australian Broadcasting Commission, 1979-1980; cuid4571; 68046 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Author's Guild, 1980; cuid4572; 68045 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Bard College, 1979-1984; cuid4573; 68044 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - British Sociological Association, 1977; cuid4574; 68043 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Cambridge University, 1976-1980; cuid4575; 68042 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Cambridge University Press (Cambridge), 1976-1981; cuid4576; 68041 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Cambridge University Press (New York), 1980-1985; cuid4577; 68040 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1976-1978; cuid4578; 68039 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Jocelyn Carlson, 1992-1993; cuid4579; 68038 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Center for Urban Affairs, 1980; cuid4580; 68037 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Century Club, 1979-1984; cuid4581; 68036 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Collège de France, 1979-1980; cuid4582; 68035 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Columbia University, 1979-1981; cuid4584; 68033 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Columbia University Press, 1977-1980; cuid4585; 68032 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Corporate Architecture Group, 1979; cuid4586; 68031 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Eastern Sociological Society, 1977-1979; cuid4587; 68030 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Ecole des Hautes Etudes, 1976-1981; cuid4588; 68029 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Editions du Seuil, 1978-1980; cuid4589; 68028 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Editions Recherches, 1980; cuid4590; 68027 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Editorial Kairós, 1977; cuid4591; 68026 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Esprit, undated; cuid4592; 68025 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Faber and Faber, 1979-1986; cuid4593; 68024 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Farrar, Straus & Giroux Inc., 1979-1984; cuid4594; 68023 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Fayard, 1984-1986; cuid4595; 68022 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Feltrinelli Edetore, 1984; cuid4596; 68021 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Ford Foundation, 1974-1984; cuid4597; 68020 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - The French-America Foundation, 1980; cuid4598; 68019 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Paul and Peter Fritz AG, 1984-1985; cuid4599; 68018 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Geo Magazine, 1984; cuid4600; 68017 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - David R. Goldine, Inc., 1984-1985; cuid4601; 68016 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1978-1980; cuid4602; 68015 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Granada Television International, Ltd., 1979; cuid4603; 68014 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Hardy Holzman Pfeiffer Associates, undated; cuid4604; 68013 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Harper's, 1984-1985; cuid4605; 68012 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Harvard Educational Review, 1977; cuid4606; 68011 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Harvard University, 1980-1984; cuid4607; 68010 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1981-1984; cuid4608; 68009 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Harvard University Press, 1979-1984; cuid4609; 68008 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273279
    - Harvard Society of Fellows, 1978-1985; cuid4610; 68007 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Institute for Advanced Studies, 1978-1979; cuid4611; 68006 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Institute for Architecture and Urban Studies - MacNair, 1976-1979; cuid4612; 68005 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - NYU Institute of Fine Arts, 1971-1979; cuid4613; 68004 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Institute for Philosophy of Science, Psychotherapy and Ethics, undated; cuid4614; 68003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Institute for Policy Studies, 1980-1984; cuid4615; 68002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - International Creative Management, 1976-1986; cuid4616; 68001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - International Federation of Chemical Worker's Unions, 1978; cuid4617; 68000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - International Society for the Comparative Study of Civilizations, undated; cuid4618; 67999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - International Society of Political Psychology, 1978; cuid4619; 67998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Jovanovich Harcourt, Brace/William, 1981; cuid4620; 67997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Kenyon Review, 1980-1981; cuid4621; 67996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - London Review of Books, 1981; cuid4622; 67995 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - London School of Economics, 1980-1981; cuid4623; 67994 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Lyon Université, 1980; cuid4624; 67993 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1980; cuid4625; 67992 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1977-1986; cuid4626; 67991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Miami University, 1982; cuid4627; 67990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Minuit Revue Périodique, 1980; cuid4628; 67989 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Le Monde, 1980; cuid4629; 67988 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - The Nation, 1982; cuid4630; 67987 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - The National Book Critics Circle, 1982; cuid4631; 67986 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1978-1984; cuid4632; 67985 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - National Gay Task Force, 1981; cuid4633; 67984 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - National Science Foundation, 1978-1980; cuid4634; 67983 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - National Science Foundation, 1976-1980; cuid4635; 67982 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - National Science Foundation, undated; cuid4636; 67981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273287
    - New York Review of Books, 1977-1985; cuid4637; 67980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - New York Times, 1978-1986; cuid4638; 67979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - New York Times Book Review, 1979-1983; cuid4639; 67978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - The New Yorker, 1978-1986; cuid4640; 67977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Newsweek, 1981; cuid4641; 67976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Partisan Review, 1979; cuid4642; 67975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - PEN, 1977-1981; cuid4643; 67974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Oxford University Press, 1979-1986; cuid4644; 67973 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Pantheon Books, 1978-1984; cuid4645; 67972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Princeton University, 1982-1986; cuid4646; 67971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Review of Existentialist Psychology & Psychiatry, 1977; cuid4647; 67970 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - David Riesman Festschrift, 1976-1979; cuid4648; 67969 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1979-1981; cuid4649; 67968 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - The Rockefeller University, 1978; cuid4650; 67967 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Deborah Rogers Ltd., 1976-1986; cuid4651; 67966 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Royal Institute of British Architects, 1983-1984; cuid4652; 67965 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Moshe Safdie & Associates, 1980-1986; cuid4653; 67964 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Secker & Warburg, 1980-1981; cuid4654; 67963 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Signs Journal of Women in Culture & Society, 1980; cuid4655; 67962 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Kalman Silvert Festschrift, 1977-1978; cuid4656; 67961 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Simon & Schuster, Inc., 1979; cuid4657; 67960 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Société Européenne de Culture, 1980; cuid4658; 67959 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Society of Fellows, New York University, 1978-1985; cuid4659; 67958 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Social and Public Art Resource Center SPARC, 1976-1980; cuid4660; 67957 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Southwestern at Memphis, 1977; cuid4661; 67956 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273295
    - Theory & Society, 1976-1979; cuid4663; 67954 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Times Literary Supplement, 1980; cuid4664; 67953 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - The Tocqueville Association, 1977-1978; cuid4665; 67952 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Transaction Publishers, 1983; cuid4666; 67951 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Trinity College, 1976-1977; cuid4667; 67950 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Tuttle-Mori Agency, 1985-1986; cuid4668; 67949 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Vanity Fair, 1982-1983; cuid4669; 67948 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Viking Press, 1979; cuid4670; 67947 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Vogue Magazine, 1984; cuid4671; 67946 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Voices, 1982; cuid4672; 67945 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Yale Law School, 1981-1983; cuid4673; 67944 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Subseries D: Subject Files, 67844
    - Before Stonewall, 1982; cuid4674; 67942 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Bellagio Conference on Humanities and Social Thought, 1974-1976; cuid4675; 67941 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Bucharest Conference, 1977; cuid4676; 67940 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Norman Cantor: "The Dream Deferred", 1980; cuid4677; 67939 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Chrysler Forum, 1979; cuid4678; 67938 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Cornell University - Society for the Humanities, 1979; cuid4679; 67937 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - The Council on Foundations Conference, 1984-1985; cuid4680; 67936 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Conference of Europeanists, 1979; cuid4681; 67935 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Douglas/Wollaeger - Towards a Typology of the Viewing Public, 1980; cuid4682; 67934 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Exxon, 1977-1984; cuid4684; 67932 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Fall of Public Man, 1974-1983; cuid4685; 67931 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Family Educational Rights & Privacy Act of, 1980; cuid4686; 67930 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Freud Lecture, 1976-1977; cuid4687; 67929 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Goldberger-Freud Project, 1976; cuid4688; 67928 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Graz Literary Festival Frankfurt/London, 1983-1984; cuid4689; 67927 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - The Human Figure on the Stage & in the Street Exhibit, 1974-1976; cuid4691; 67925 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273303
    - International Sociology Meeting, 1978; cuid4692; 67924 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - International Distributive Justice Ronald Findlay, 1981; cuid4693; 67923 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Jerusalem, 1981; cuid4694; 67922 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Frances Myrna Kamm "Equal Concern and Respect for Unequal Numbers", 1981; cuid4695; 67921 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Ambassador Theater, 1985; cuid4696; 67920 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Barrymore Theater Exterior, 1987; cuid4697; 67919 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Belasco Theater Interior, 1987; cuid4698; 67918 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Belasco Theater Exterior, 1987; cuid4699; 67917 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Biltmore Theater Interior, 1987; cuid4700; 67916 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Booth Theater Exterior, 1987; cuid4701; 67915 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Broadhurst Theater Exterior, 1987; cuid4702; 67914 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Brooks Atkinson Exterior, 1987; cuid4703; 67913 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Cort Theater Exterior, 1987; cuid4704; 67912 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Embassy I Theater, 1987; cuid4705; 67911 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Eugene O'Neill Theater, 1987; cuid4706; 67910 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Forty-Sixth Street Exterior, 1987; cuid4707; 67909 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Gerard Hotel Exterior, 1982; cuid4708; 67908 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Golden Theater Exterior, 1987; cuid4709; 67907 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Henry Miller Theater, 1987; cuid4710; 67906 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Hudson Theater, 1987; cuid4711; 67905 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Imperial Theater, 1987; cuid4712; 67904 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Landmarks Preservation - The Lamb's Club, 1974; cuid4713; 67903 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Landmarks Preservation - The Little Theater, 1987; cuid4714; 67902 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Longacre Theater Exterior, 1987; cuid4715; 67901 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Lunt-Fontaine, 1987; cuid4716; 67900 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Lyceum Theater, 1987; cuid4717; 67899 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Majestic Theater, 1987; cuid4718; 67898 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273311
    - Landmarks Preservation - Music Theater Exterior, 1987; cuid4719; 67897 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Landmarks Preservation - New Amsterdam Theater, 1979; cuid4720; 67896 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Plymouth Theatre, 1987; cuid4721; 67895 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Royale Theater Exterior, 1987; cuid4722; 67894 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Landmarks Preservation - St. James Theater, 1987; cuid4723; 67893 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Palace Theater, 1987; cuid4724; 67892 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Schubert Theater Exterior, 1987; cuid4725; 67891 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Town Hall, 1978; cuid4726; 67890 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Landmarks Preservation - Winter Garden Theater, 1988; cuid4727; 67889 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - University of Michigan "Narcissism in Modern Society", 1977; cuid4728; 67888 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - NY Office of Midtown Enforcement Annual Report, 1986; cuid4729; 67887 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - NY Office of Midtown Enforcement Annual Report, 1987; cuid4730; 67886 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - NYC Crime Statistics - Midtown Precincts, 1987-1988; cuid4731; 67885 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Music and Sociology (ASA/Aspen), 1975-1977; cuid4732; 67884 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - National Endowment for the Arts Proposal, 1983; cuid4733; 67883 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - National Town Meeting, 1980; cuid4734; 67882 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - New Republic Letters re: Sontag, 1982; cuid4735; 67881 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - The New Right and Current Affairs, undated; cuid4736; 67880 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - New School for Social Research Graduate Faculty, undated; cuid4737; 67879 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Participation & Disorder in Urban Form Conference, 1979; cuid4738; 67878 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - PEN Freedom to Write, undated; cuid4739; 67877 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - PEN Human Rights, 1978; cuid4740; 67876 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - PEN Lease, 1978-1981; cuid4741; 67875 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - PEN Nominations for Officers and Board, 1978-1979; cuid4742; 67874 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Penguin Books, 1976; cuid4743; 67873 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1982-1985; cuid4744; 67872 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Press Clippings, 1978-1980; cuid4745; 67871 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273329
    - Press Clippings, 1979-1984; cuid4746; 67870 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Public Sexuality and Hiding Behavior D.A. Karp, 1971; cuid4747; 67869 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Publishers - France, 1975-1982; cuid4748; 67868 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Publishers - Italian, 1975-1982; cuid4749; 67867 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Publishers - German, 1977-1982; cuid4750; 67866 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Recontres Internationales de Geneve, 1979; cuid4751; 67865 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Random House, 1977-1980; cuid4752; 67864 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Red Markings, 1982; cuid4753; 67863 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Claude Roquin Translation Paperwork, 1980; cuid4754; 67862 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Moshe Safdie Exhibition Catalog, 1982; cuid4755; 67861 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Moshe Safdie Lecture & Exhibit Correspondence, 1982; cuid4756; 67860 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Fellows' Scrapbook, 1986; cuid4757; 67859 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - George Segal Liberation Sculpture, 1980; cuid4758; 67858 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Richard Sennett Essays and Transcripts, undated; cuid4759; 67857 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273337
    - Richard Sennett Essays and Transcripts, undated; cuid4760; 67856 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Robert R. Holt: Sennett Proposal for "Personality, Moral Development, and the Humanities", 1977; cuid4761; 67855 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Soviet Union Visit, 1989; cuid4762; 67854 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - NYU Office of Sponsored Programs, 1975-1982; cuid4763; 67853 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - The Theory of the State, undated; cuid4764; 67852 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Virgil Thomson "Music Does Not Flow", undated; cuid4765; 67851 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - De Tocqueville Conference, 1981; cuid4766; 67850 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Triumph or Downfall of Civil Society Alain Touraine, undated; cuid4767; 67849 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - UNESCO American Embassy Residence, 1979; cuid4768; 67848 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Judith R. Walkowitz "Jack the Ripper & the Myth of Male Violence", 1982; cuid4769; 67847 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Wellfleet Meetings, 1980; cuid4770; 67846 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Work in America: A Decade Later (Ford Foundation), 1978; cuid4771; 67845 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Series II: Seminars, Lectures and Events, 67631
  - Acting in Everyday Life and Everyday Life in Acting Victor Turner, undated; cuid4772; 67842 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - The Actor As a Celebrity Richard Gilman, undated; cuid4773; 67841 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Quentin Anderson Symposium, 1982; cuid4774; 67840 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Anthropological Aspects of Television, 1980; cuid4775; 67839 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Architecture in New York, 1981; cuid4776; 67838 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Architecture of Confinement (Tom Bender), 1979; cuid4777; 67837 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273345
  - Arendt Conference, 1979; cuid4778; 67836 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Arendt Conference, 1980-1981; cuid4779; 67835 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Auden Festival, 1983; cuid4780; 67834 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Auden Festival Invitations, 1983; cuid4781; 67832 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Auden Festival Accounts, 1983-1984; cuid4782; 67833 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Auden Festival Publicity, 1983; cuid4783; 67831 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Authority Conference, 1977-1978; cuid4784; 67830 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Roland Barthes Conference, 1983; cuid4785; 67829 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Charles A. Beard Conference, 1981-1982; cuid4786; 67828 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Jessica Benjamin Seminar, 1986-1987; cuid4787; 67827 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273352
  - Ronald Blythe Lecture, 1979-1980; cuid4788; 67826 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Biography Seminar, 1981-1985; cuid4789; 67825 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Biography Seminar Budget, undated; cuid4790; 67824 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Biography Seminar - Meeting Summaries, 1980-1981; cuid4791; 67823 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Biography Seminar Readings, undated; cuid4792; 67822 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Biography Seminar Readings, undated; cuid4793; 67821 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Book Parties (Receptions), 1983; cuid4794; 67820 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Jorge Luis Borges Seminar, 1982; cuid4795; 67819 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Borges Lecture, 1982; cuid4796; 67818 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Borges Events RSVPs, 1982; cuid4797; 67817 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Breyten Breytenbach, 1984; cuid4798; 67816 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Censorship Conference, 1980-1981; cuid4799; 67815 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Censorship Conference Transcript, 1980; cuid4800; 67814 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273360
  - Commercial Culture Seminar, 1986; cuid4801; 67813 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Communism, undated; cuid4802; 67812 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Communism and the Intellectual Seminar, 1981; cuid4803; 67811 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - A Program in Comparative Cultural Studies, 1980-1981; cuid4804; 67810 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Constructing America, 1985-1987; cuid4805; 67809 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Constructing America Readings, 1987-1988; cuid4806; 67808 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Culture and the Actor, 1979-1980; cuid4807; 67807 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Culture and the Actor - Roger Shattuck, 1980; cuid4808; 67806 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Culture and Economics, 1984-1986; cuid4809; 67805 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Culture of Cities, 1979; cuid4810; 67804 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Culture of Cities, 1980; cuid4811; 67803 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273378
  - Culture of Cities, 1981; cuid4812; 67802 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Culture of Cities - General, undated; cuid4813; 67801 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Natalie Zemon Davis Lecture, 1978-1979; cuid4814; 67800 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Daniel Defert Symposium, 1981-1982; cuid4815; 67799 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Jacques Derrida "The Law of Genre", 1979; cuid4816; 67798 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - An Evening of Brahms, 1984; cuid4817; 67797 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Exiled Writers Program, 1980; cuid4818; 67796 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fellows Lunches, 1980-1982; cuid4819; 67795 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Fellows Lunches - Speakers, 1993; cuid4820; 67794 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fellows Meetings, 1977-1983; cuid4821; 67793 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273386
  - Fiscal Crisis in New York City, 1981; cuid4822; 67792 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Foucault Conference, 1985; cuid4823; 67791 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Foucault/Habermas, 1981; cuid4824; 67790 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Freedom and Censorship in the Schools, 1981; cuid4825; 67789 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Friday Lunch Seminars, 1987-1988; cuid4826; 67788 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Future of the Intellectual in New York, 1976; cuid4827; 67787 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1979-1980; cuid4828; 67786 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1981; cuid4829; 67785 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1982; cuid4830; 67784 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1985; cuid4831; 67783 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Gallatin Lectures: Edmund Leach, 1982-1983; cuid4832; 67782 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Gallatin Lectures: Edward Stankiewicz, 1982-1983; cuid4833; 67781 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Galway Kinnell Readings, undated; cuid4835; 67779 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Gemant Lecture on Science and the Humanities, 1990; cuid4836; 67778 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Geopolitics of Information (Anthony Smith), 1980; cuid4837; 67777 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Anthony Giddens: From Marx to Nietzsche?, 1981; cuid4838; 67776 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Phillip Glass, 1981-1982; cuid4839; 67775 (Box 21, Folder 19)